Thank you for watching!
Good morning.
Today, we are going to have a talk.
It's a free talk.
Free talk?
You can eat the black beard kiki in
front of you.
If you miss it, you will get angry.
I will get angry?
It's like now.
I'm not angry.
Are you a tofu mental?
You are introducing the topic.
We have prepared a talk and a black
beard kiki.
I see.
You can talk and insert the black beard
kiki if you want.
You can order it.
You can start with Sakura and go back
in order.
If you don't have it, you are good at
talking.
If you are in trouble, there is a
trumpet to decide the topic.
You can play the trumpet.
What are you doing?
How far are you going?
Let's start.
It's a little rough.
It was rough from the last time.
Is there anything to do?
Yes.
The birthday party is on October 16th.
I'm wondering what to do.
I will give you a present.
What are you doing?
I see.
It's too early.
You are too early.
I didn't expect you to be so quick.
You are amazing.
I understood the rules.
I was surprised and angry.
I want to ask you two.
What do you want to ask?
I'm wondering if I should play the
songs that everyone knows or play the
songs that I know.
I'm worried about that.
How about you, Mon?
I want to play the songs that I like.
What is that advice?
You should know better.
What are you doing?
You can enjoy it a little more.
Why are you so quick?
It's a bad product.
I see.
What is it?
Start again.
What was it?
Do you want to do the song you want to
do?
I want to do the song I want to do.
There was a song that the audience
could enjoy.
I mixed it up.
But it's my birthday, so I'm happy to
be told anything.
Certainly, it's a reward.
I thought you might not know.
I thought there was a person who would
be very happy if I did it.
I see.
I want to hear his favorite song.
Certainly.
That's a reward.
I want to play the trumpet.
It's too early.
I want to play it.
Would you like to play one?
I want to see what it's like.
I want to play it.
Which one do you like?
Black.
Red.
I'll play it.
This.
The person on the left will tickle you
for 10 seconds.
I can't tickle you because I'm not on
the left.
I'll be right back.
Please.
I don't want to.
She's tickling.
It's been a while since I did it.
The trumpet is good.
It's not a topic of conversation, is
it?
I don't care.
I thought there might be a story behind
it.
But there were many things that weren't
the story.
I see.
Is this the story?
What should I do?
It's a penalty.
Introduce yourself in a word.
My story?
It's not a story.
My name is Sakura Hinano.
What's your name?
I am...
Good.
Rinekita.
Rinekita?
Rinetaki.
No.
It's not a word.
Who?
My name is...
I am Karen Tachibana.
Do you know?
Tachibana?
This card is bad.
That's right.
I'll praise the person in front of me.
I'll praise the person next to me.
I'll praise you first.
I like this kind of thing.
I've said it before, but I'll praise
you seriously.
I really like your singing voice.
Really?
I like the chorus of the song you
covered.
I get goose bumps every time I hear it.
I'm glad.
I like that part and your singing
voice.
Thank you.
I feel like you're changing your
singing style every time you take
lessons.
I can feel that you are always studying
and singing.
I'm noticed by Karen.
I'm noticed by you.
I'm watching you.
I thought you were going to say that.
I'm thinking about it.
Thank you.
I prepared a red card.
Let's play the music.
I'm going to tell you a embarrassing
story.
Embarrassing story?
I think there are many.
When I was on the elevator in this
costume, a young man came in and I could
see him.
I can see that.
I asked him, is this your private
clothes?
He said, no, this is for shooting.
I said, good luck.
I was embarrassed.
It's my private clothes.
I thought so.
I wondered how he would react.
But, he said, this is for shooting.
I was embarrassed to get angry with
this.
I'm embarrassed to look back.
I think there are many.
When I went to the office, the staff
was having a meeting on Zoom.
I was wearing earphones.
I didn't know that.
I was greeting and sitting down.
I was working.
I was sleeping.
I said something.
I thought I said it.
I replied it.
He didn't reply at all.
I looked around and he was wearing
earphones.
I was embarrassed.
I said, are you in the meeting?
I was not seen by anyone.
I was embarrassed.
At that moment.
The staff was in a position where I
couldn't see him.
I thought it was a new song.
I said, it's a good song.
He didn't reply at all.
I thought he was in the meeting.
I went to see him.
He didn't do anything.
I asked him, did you ignore me?
He said, yes.
Did you really ignore me?
What?
I was embarrassed.
You were cute.
I asked him, did you ignore me?
He was embarrassed.
He was in a position where I couldn't
see him.
I was embarrassed.
Next, we'll see the next video.
I want to see it.
What?
I've never seen him with his tongue
out.
I think he is cute.
He is cute.
The mushroom on his head is cute.
It's real.
It's like 3D.
His outfit is cute.
He is cute.
Everyone has different styles.
He can slide.
He is cute.
He is mysterious.
Yuno doesn't like mushrooms.
He is good.
He is a beauty.
He is cute.
He is green.
Everyone is cute.
He is amazing.
The name is cute.
I want to do it.
It's like a tattoo of RINNE.
It's cute.
It's definitely cute.
He is amazing.
Did you see the video?
I didn't see it.
I want to see it.
Will you show me?
He is amazing.
Please subscribe to this channel!
Hurry up and show me!
I've never seen a logo like this.
It's so cute.
Isn't it cute?
Is this a photo card?
You can post it on YouTube.
I see.
This is important.
I want this.
You look like an idol.
I've never seen them.
I agree.
It's so cute.
I'm curious about the logo.
The mushroom is cute.
The letters are coming out of the
house.
It's cute.
You look like a talker.
I like it.
Please come and see us.
We have a daily update.
I'd be happy if you could come in.
We'll do our best.
The next talk theme is
Show your charm point.
Mine is my hair.
I think it's really black.
You can tell by comparing it.
I think I can tell by comparing it to
Mon-chan.
Can you tell?
I don't know.
I can tell.
Can you really tell?
It's totally different.
I can tell by the sunlight.
It's really black.
Did you get angry?
I've never been angry.
When you're angry, be calm.
Like this.
Everyone.
It's a secret.
How should I get angry?
Like Naoki Hanzo.
You can get angry like him.
I can get angry like him.
I don't think I can do it.
Isn't it amazing?
I'm trying to make you angry.
You're right.
I'm wearing purple.
I'm not saying it because I'm a man.
You're a man.
I'm a man.
Yeah!!!
The next topic is...
Telling a secret.
Secret?
It's a secret.
I think so.
I don't know who gave me this, but I
had a pair of socks at home.
I think it was a member's.
I thought I should give it back to her.
But I didn't.
So, I went somewhere.
I can't go back.
Do you have any?
It's a secret, isn't it?
I'll tell you one more.
What is it?
I'm so secretive.
Keep telling me.
I think I've said it somewhere.
When I was in elementary school, I
wanted to be a chef.
I had to tell the staff when I cut my
hair.
I thought I shouldn't make it.
I took out a little bit of hair and
held a pair of scissors.
I looked in the mirror and said,
Oh, my God!
I said,
I cut one of my hair.
And I sent a message to the staff.
I said, I'm sorry. I cut my hair by
mistake.
I thought it would be better to cut
both of my hair.
So, I cut my hair.
This is a secret.
What's that? It's funny.
I wanted to be a chef.
You admire it, don't you?
I wanted to be a chef when I was in
elementary school.
So, I cut my hair.
I didn't tell you.
I'm sorry.
It's a secret.
I didn't want to waste my time.
You're fast.
When I was in elementary school, I
didn't want to waste a second.
In class, the teacher starts talking.
I talked a lot.
I talked about love.
I thought it was a waste of time.
So, I took clay in a toolbox.
When the teacher started talking, I
started making food samples in the
toolbox.
I also brought Tamagotchi to school.
I brought cat food.
I remember I packed it up tightly so
that I wouldn't waste it.
When I was in elementary school, I was
lucky to be talked about by the teacher.
I was lucky.
But, I was a waste of time.
I was kind to the teacher.
I was a teenager who wanted to do that.
But, no one noticed it.
I didn't tell my friends that I brought
it.
I didn't tell them.
You're right.
You're a good girl.
I'm not a good girl.
You're right.
The secret of school.
School...
It's a secret.
It's a scary story.
I talked to Rinne on LINE the other
day.
I was sleeping and I saw a white thing
flying around.
I thought it was a trash but it was
flying again.
I was talking to her and suddenly I saw
a white thing flying.
I didn't know what it was.
I was like, what?
I couldn't understand what was going
on.
I heard a white thing was flying.
It was flying three times.
What is this?
I don't know.
It's a trash.
Next.
I'll talk about my dream.
You don't want to see it?
What?
Can I see it?
You can keep it open.
I'll do my best to be with you as long
as I can in TOKUSAN.
I'll do my best to be with you in
BUDOKAN and in the future.
I'll do my best to be with you as long
as I can in TOKUSAN.
Do you have any dream?
Yes.
I'm afraid of shaking.
Is that so?
What is your dream?
You can say what you want to say.
I can say only yes.
I think so, too.
Great!
Please say yes to your dream.
Yes.
It's easy to understand.
I'm afraid of breaking.
I'm sure you are.
Great!
It's easy to understand.
Why?
You can say yes to anything.
I didn't understand.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Today, we did a free talk and did a
Q&A.
It was fun.
We talked slowly.
We didn't talk together.
We talked together or someone talked
alone.
We talked with these three.
Please subscribe to this channel.
We are KAI.
We got the last one.
I'm glad that we got the last one.
Thank you for watching this video.
Thank you.
How was it? Did you have fun?
We were the only ones who talked.
We couldn't talk because we were
talking about KAI.
Please look forward to the next video.
We are KANE, MON-CHAN and KINU.
Bye bye.